bryaneisenberg.com 2012-06-22

# Privacy Policy Guarantee

### We value your privacy!

We will never give, lease, sell or otherwise disclose your personal information. Period! Any information you give to Eisenberg Holdings, LLC at any of our sites (including: [http://www.bryaneisenberg.com](http://www.bryaneisenberg.com.com/) or [www.websitetestingtools.com](http://www.websitetestingtools.com/)) will be held with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways to which you have not consented. A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard your personal information is described below. If you have any questions at all about our privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.bryaneisenberg.com/contact/ "Contact Bryan Or Jeffrey Eisenberg").

 **Resale or disclosure of information to third parties**

Eisenberg Holdings, LLC does not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any personal information collected at our site, including contact forms, download requests or email lists unless otherwise specified on the page you subscribed from.

 **Browser information collected on the web site**

Eisenberg Holdings, LLC analyzes the web site logs to improve the value of the materials available on the web site.

 **Privacy of our email lists**

Individuals must affirmatively ask to join our mailing lists using the forms provided on this web site or other means expressly sanctioned by Eisenberg Holdings, LLC. We do not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease the addresses on our list to  
anyone. In addition, we configure our list server software to refuse to divulge the email addresses of our list subscribers to anyone but authorized Eisenberg Holdings, LLC staff, including other list subscribers.

 **Unsubscribe Policy  
**We strive to only send e-mail to those who want to receive it. If you would not like to receive future e-mails from us, click on the **UNSUBSCRIBE** link in the footer of the email.
